manidoo.com 2013-04-10

# Manidoo's Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

**Effective Date: March 1, 2008,**

www.manidoo.com is owned and operated by Manidoo Holdings. Please take a moment to read this Privacy Policy which applies to your visit to www.manidoo.com (the “Site”). By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of your information by us in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, then do not use the Site. 

**Changes to the Privacy Policy**   
We reserve the right to change the terms of this Privacy Policy. Since any changes will be posted on this page, we encourage you to check this page regularly. If we make changes, we will indicate at the top of this page the as modified date. We may also notify you of such changes by email or notice on our home page. Your continued use of the Site following any changes to this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such changes. Unless otherwise stated, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account. If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, you should first contact us at [privacy@manidoo.com ](mailto:privacy@manidoo.com) or at the address below. 

**Information We Collect**   
We may collect “personally identifiable information” from you, such as your name, address, telephone number, fax number and email address. We will collect personally identifiable information from you when you actively give us the information, such as when you register to become a member, request to receive newsletters, or otherwise communicate with the Site. 

When you join the Site membership, or use other features on the Site, such as purchasing a product or service, we request that you provide financial information, such as account or credit card numbers. We will use your financial information to bill you for products and services or otherwise process your transactions. By making a purchase on the Site, you consent to our providing your financial information to our service providers and to such third parties as we determine is necessary to process your transactions. These third parties may include the credit card companies and banking institutions used to process the transaction. 

We may also collect demographic information that you provide to us, such as your zip code, income level, birth date, birth place, birth time, education level, occupation, gender and industry. We use your demographic information to tailor the Site to you, to contact you with updates, news alerts and discounts, and for internal purposes. 

We may collect “non-personally identifiable information,” such as your Web site browsing patterns, IP address, ISP and browser type. We collect non-personally identifiable information from you by “passive” means, often through the use of clear gifs and cookies. In addition, third-party advertisers may also use cookies and clear gifs to collect non-personal information from you. We have no control over information collected by third-party advertisers. This Privacy Policy covers the use of clear gifs and cookies by us and does not cover the use of cookies or other tracking technologies by third-party advertisers. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. We use session ID cookies to confirm that users are logged in. These cookies terminate once the user closes the browser. By default, we use a persistent cookie that stores your information to make it easier for you to login when you come back to the Site. You can remove or block this cookie using the settings in your browser if you want to disable this convenience feature. 

**Not for Children**   
This Site is not intended for use by children. We will not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information submitted by visitors to the Site who are under the age of 18. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 18, we will delete that information. We recommend that minors below the age of 18 ask their parents for permission before sending any information about themselves to anyone over the Internet. 

**How We Use Your Information**   
We may use your personally identifiable information to set up your account, for customer service, to provide you with information, newsletters and news alerts and to customize your experience on the Site. Your personal information is also used by us to respond to your requests, process your transactions on the Site, tailor offerings to you and send you information about membership benefits. 

In addition to Manidoo newsletters, you also have the option of receiving newsletters from third parties. If you choose to receive a third-party newsletter, we will send any required contact information to the third-party provider of that newsletter. 

We may use your personally identifiable information to contact you with information we think you may be interested in. If you do not want to receive this information or newsletters from us, email us at [privacy@manidoo.com](mailto:privacy@manidoo.com). Email messages will also provide you with an opportunity to opt-out of receiving this information. Please note that changes to your preferences may not be effective immediately. If you change your mind later and would like to receive information and newsletters from us again, email us at [privacy@manidoo.com](mailto:privacy@manidoo.com). We reserve the right to send you notices about your account even if you opt-out of all voluntary email notifications. 

We may use third party contractors to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as authorization of credit card transactions, shipping, administration of sweepstakes and contests, or email service, and we may share your information with these contractors for those limited purposes. 

We share information we collect from you with third-parties and our affiliated companies for their direct marketing purposes. California Residents Only: If you are a resident of California and you do not want us to share your information with third parties and our affiliated companies for marketing purposes, please email us at [privacy@manidoo.com](mailto:privacy@manidoo.com)

We may use your personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information we collect from you to provide you with advertising and offers specifically for you. We may also match your personally identifiable information with third-party data for advertising purposes. If you do not want us to use your information for targeted advertisements please email us at [privacy@manidoo.com](mailto:privacy@manidoo.com). If you change your mind later, you can email us at [privacy@manidoo.com ](mailto:privacy@manidoo.com) . If Manidoo Holdings is sold to, or merges with, another company, or declares bankruptcy, some or all of the personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information collected from you may be transferred to a third party as a result of the transfer of assets. We may also disclose your personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information when we determine it is necessary to comply with applicable laws or protect the interests or safety of Manidoo Holdings or other visitors to the Site. 

We use non-personally identifiable information for internal purposes and to help us interact with visitors to the Site. We may also share non-personally identifiable information in the aggregate form with third parties to illustrate trends and patterns. 

**Links and Software Downloads**   
The Site may contain links to other sites, including, among others, those of advertisers, other third parties and companies whose trademarks may appear on the Site. In addition, the Site may allow you to download software. We are not responsible for the information collection practices or the content of the sites to which we link or of the software you download from the Site. 

**Heightened Security**   
For your convenience, we provide a way for you to recover a lost password or user name via a webpage. However, if you select the “heightened security” option in your account preferences, your ability to recover a lost password or user name will be disabled. If you enable heightened security, no one (including you) can search for your login information and view it online. 

**Community Functions**   
The Site may make available to its users chat rooms, forums, message/discussion boards and/or other community functions, such as communities which enable you to create a personal profile. Remember that any information you disclose in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal, financial, or other information. You should use such community functions at your own risk. If you post a message on a message/discussion board, your user name will appear hyperlinked on the board to allow other users to email you. Our Site is designed to allow members to contact you via email without revealing your email address. This Site may include a chat function. The chat function is administered by a third party and is subject to the third party’s own privacy practices. Your use of the chat function and any information collected from you during such use is governed by the Privacy Policy of Meebo available at [http://blog.meebo.com/privacy ](http://blog.meebo.com/privacy) and is not governed by this Privacy Policy. We are not responsible for the information collection practices or the content of the chat function. 

All news provided in Manidoo Café comes from third-party RSS feeds, and Manidoo is not responsible for the content of this news. We are not responsible for the information collection practices or the content of the RSS feeds. Please refer to the respective RSS feeds for their individual privacy policies. Your use of the RSS feeds and any information collected from you during such use is not governed by this Privacy Policy. 

**Posting Content**   
You post content on the Site at your own risk. We cannot control the actions of other users with whom you may choose to share your profile information. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that user content you post on the Site will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Site. You understand and acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of your posted content and profile may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if other users have copied or stored your content and profile. 

**Tell-a-Friend and E-Cards**   
We may offer you the option to invite your friends to join our services. If you invite a friend to join, we will request that you provide us with the name and email address of your friend. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the Site. We may also offer you the option to send e-cards. When sending e-cards, we also request the email address and name of the intended e-card recipient. We may share the names and email addresses from our tell-a-friend and e-card services with third parties and our affiliated companies for direct marketing purposes. Your friend may contact us at [privacy@manidoo.com ](mailto:privacy@manidoo.com) to request that we remove this information from our database. California Residents Only: If you are a resident of California and you do not want us to share this information with third parties and our affiliated companies for marketing purposes, please email us at [privacy@manidoo.com](mailto:privacy@manidoo.com). Security 

Protecting your information is important to us. When you enter financial information, such as a credit card number, on any order form, the information is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL). In addition, we use industry standard technology to protect the security of your information. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we are committed to protecting your information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us. 

**Contact Us**   
Please contact us with any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy at: 

Manidoo Holdings   
167 Cherry St. PMB 292,   
Milford, CT 06460-3400   
Email address: [privacy@manidoo.com ](mailto:privacy@manidoo.com)
